David E. Lilienthal Papers, 1900-1981 (bulk 1950-1981 ): Inventory MC148
EADs for public policy collection from import batch
- Series 18: Correspondence and Related Materials, 1905 October 19-1981; 208 boxes; 2 items
  - Subseries 18C: 1955-1958, 15 boxes
    - Berle, Adolf A., Jr, 1955; 1 box (Box 396)
    - Black, Eugene R, 1955; 1 box (Box 396)
    - Bradbury, N.E., 1955; 1 box (Box 396)
    - Carrier Corporation, 1955; 1 box (Box 396)
    - Clapp, Gordon R, 1955; 1 box (Box 396)
    - Clement, Frank G, 1955; 1 box (Box 396)
    - Re Coal, 1955; 1 box (Box 396)
    - Collier's, 1955; 1 box (Box 396)
    - Colombia CVC (Corporacion Autonoma Regional del Cauca), 1955; 1 box (Box 397)
    - Re Commercial Petroleum Transport Co, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Re Commercial Transport, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Cooke, Morris L, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Council on Foreign Relations: Study Group on Nuclear Weapons, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Democratic Party - New York, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Denson, John, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - DePauw University, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Ebtehaj, A.H., 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - English Speaking Union, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Federation of American Scientists, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Franklin, John C, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Freedom House, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Gunther, John, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Hancock, John M, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Harper & Brothers, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Harvard University, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Henderson, Frances, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Hill, Lister, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Hoover, Calvin B, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Hough, Henry and Betty, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Re India, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Re Iran, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Re Italy, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Re Japan, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Kaplan, J.M., 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Kefauver, Estes, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Kissinger, Henry A.: Council on Foreign Relations, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - La Follette, Philip F, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Lazard Freres & Co, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Lilienthal, David E.: Notes and Drafts, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Lincoln, Murray D, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - McCloy, Whn J, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Matsumoto, Shigeharu, 1955; 1 box (Box 398)
    - Mayor's Advisory Council, New York, New York, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - Minerals & Chemicals Corporation, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - Miscellaneous, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - Re Morocco, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - Murrow, Edward R, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - National Industrial Conference Board, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - New York Academy of Osteopathy - Foundation for Research, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - Nicely, James Mount, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - O'Brian, John Lord, 1955; 1 box (Box 399)
    - Re Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Oxnam, Bishop G. Bromley, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Pace, Frank, Jr, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Patent Trademark and Copyright Foundation, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Perkins, Milo, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Pollard, William G, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Radcliffe College, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Radio Corporation of America (RCA), 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Ramey, James T, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Reston, James, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Richberg, Donald R, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Rockefeller, John D., III, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin D, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Foundation, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Roosevelt, James, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Sarnoff, David, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Sengier, Edgar, 1955; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Seymour, Walton, 1955; 1 box
      - Re Speeches by David E. Lilienthal, 1955 February 16-April 12; 1 box
        - American Institute of Mining and Metallurgical Engineers, 1955 February 16; 1 box (Box 400)
        - Athens College, Athens A Alabama, "Valley With a Future,", 1955 April 12; 1 box (Box 400)
    - Stapleton, William, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Strauss, Lewis L, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Supplee, Henderson, Jr, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Swope, Gerard, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Sylvester, Arthur, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1955; 1 box
      - Dixon-Yates Power Contract, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 401)
      - Financing, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 401)
      - Forestry, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 401)
      - General, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 401)
      - Visit by David E. Lilienthal, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Thomas, Morgan, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Truman., Harry S, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Volpe, Joseph, Jr, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Re Water, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Waymauk, William W, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Weil, George L, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Wyman, Bernice B, 1955; 1 box (Box 401)
    - Acheson, Dean, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Alldredge, J. Haden, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Allen, Forrest, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - American Committee on United Europe, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Anderson, Clinton P, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Arvin, Newton (Fred), 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Re Atomic Energy, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Re Barge Lines, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Barnard, Chester I, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Black, Eugene R., Jr, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Bronk, Detlev W, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Clapp, Gordon R, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Colombia CVC (Corporacion Autonoma Regional del Cauca), 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Re Commercial Transport Corporation, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Cornell, Katharine, 1956; 1 box (Box 402)
    - Dean, Arthur, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - DePauw University, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Draffen, Luther, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Ebtehaj, A.H., 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Franklin, John, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Freedom House, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Friendly, Alfred M, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Harper & Brothers, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Harvard University, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Re Iran, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Re Italy, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Jackson, Henry M, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Re Japan, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Julian, Percy L, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Kefauver, Estes, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - King, Judson, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Linen, James A, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Matthews, C.F., 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Mayor's Advisory Council, New York, New York, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Minerals & Chemicals Corporation, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Miscellaneous, 1956; 1 box (Box 403)
    - Murrow, Edward R, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - National Industrial Conference Board, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Nicely, James Mount, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Nichols, William I, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Re Oppenheimer, A Robert, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Patent Trade-mark and Copyright Foundation, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Perkins, Milo, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Pollard, William G, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Re Publication by David E. Lilienthal, 1956; 1 box
      - TVA - Democracy on the March. Harper & Brothers - Iranian Farsi Edition, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Rabi, I.I., 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Radcliffe College, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Radio Corporation of America, (RCA), 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Ramey, James T, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Rusk Dean, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Sarnoff, David, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Shelton, Barrett, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Spedding, Frank H, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Re Speech by David E. Lilienthal, 1956 April 16; 1 box
      - La Forte, Indiana, Chamber of Commerce, 1956 April 16; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Specht, Charles A, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Stapleton, William, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Strauss, Lewis L, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Truman, Harry S, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - United States Information Agency, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Volpe, Joseph, Jr, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Wagner, Robert F., Jr, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Wilson, Carroll L, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Witte, Edwin E, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Wyman, Bernice B, 1956; 1 box (Box 404)
    - Allen, Forrest, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Re American Commercial Barge Line Company, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - American Committee on United Europe, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Arvin, Newton (Fred), 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Re Barge Lines, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Barnard, Chester I, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Baruch, Bernard M, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Bass, Neil, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Black, Eugene R, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Breckinridge, Frank, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Brown, Earl, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Clapp, Gordon R, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Cleveland Council on World Affairs, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Coit, Margaret L, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Colombia CVC (Corporacion Autonoma Regional del Cauca), 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Re Commercial Transport Corporation, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Cooke, Morris L, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
      Includes T.V.A. for Iran" by David E. Lilienthal in The Danneshjoo, February 1957.
    - Dewey, Thomas E, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Dodds, Harold W, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Donovan, William J, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Gore, Albert, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Graham, John S, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Gunther, John, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Harper & Brothers, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Harvard University, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Hill, Lister, 1957; 1 box (Box 405)
    - Re Iran, 1957; 1 box (Box 406)
    - Re Italy, 1957; 1 box (Box 406)
    - Ito, Katsumi, 1957; 1 box (Box 406)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1957; 1 box (Box 406)
    - King, Judson, 1957; 1 box (Box 406)
    - Lazard Freres & Co, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Linen, James H, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Lively, Robert A, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Marton, Elizabeth, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Minerals & Chemicals Corporation, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Miscellaneous, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Murnane, George, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Murrow, Edward R, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - National Industrial Conference Board, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Nehru, Jawharlal, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Nevins, Allan, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Nichols, William I, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Oxnam, Bishop G. Bromley, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Pace, Frank, Jr, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Re Puerto Rico, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Radcliffe College, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Radio Corporation of America (RCA), 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Ramey, James T, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Redding Ridge, Connecticut - Property, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Rockefeller, John D., III, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Schilling, Warner R, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Shelton, Barrett, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Specht, Charles A, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Spedding, F.H., 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Swope, Herbert Bayard, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Taylor, Harold, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Truman, Harry S, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - United States Information Agency, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Witte, Edwin E, 1957; 1 box (Box 407)
    - Re American Commercial Barge Line Company, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - American Committee on United Europe, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Arvin, Newton (Fred), 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Atchley, Dana Winslow, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Re Atomic Energy, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Re Barge Lines, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Baruch, Bernard M, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Benton, William, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Bischof, George P, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Black, Eugene R, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Re Brazil, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Brittain, Robert, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Bronk, Detlev W, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Carrier Corporation, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Challener, Richard D, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Clapp, Gordon R, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Cleveland Council on World Affairs, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Re Colombia CVC (Corporacion Autonoma Regional del Cauca), 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Cooke, Morris L, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Davis; Donald K, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Dean, Arthur, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Dean, Gordon, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Dillon, Douglas, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Dix, William S, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Duffus, R.L., 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Eberstadt, Ferdinand, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Ebtehaj, A.H., 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Re Egypt, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Re Ethiopia, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Re Euratom, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Finley, S.R., 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Friendly, Alfred M, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Fulbright, J. William, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Garrison, Lloyd K, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Re Ghana, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Greene, Nathan, 1958; 1 box (Box 408)
    - Harper & Brothers, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Harriman, W. Averell, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Harvard University, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Hill, Lister, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Hoffman, Claire Giannini, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Hoffman, Paul G, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Re India, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Re Indus River Basin, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Re Insurance Claim, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Re Iran, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Italconsult, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Re Italy, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Jessup, Philip C., Jr, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Lazard Freres & Co, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Lleras, Alberto, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Markel, Lester, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Re Mexico, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Meyner, Robert B, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Minerals & Chemicals Corporation, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958; 1 box (Box 409)
    - Murrow, Edward R, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Nehru, Jawaharlal, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Re Nile Waters, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Oates, Whitney J, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Re Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Oxnam, Bishop G. Bromley, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Pace, Frank, Jr, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Re Pakistan, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Peccei, Aurelia, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Radcliffe College, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Radio Corporation of America (RCA), 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Reston, James, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Richberg, Donald R, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Shules, Maxwell, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Re Somalia, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Re Speech by David E. Lilienthal, 1958 September 9; 1 box
      - American Chemical Society. "Science and Man,", 1958 September 9; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Strauss, Lewis L, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Re Sudan, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Tavener, Charles H, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
      Includes Twenty-fifth Anniversary files.
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Re Valparaiso, Indiana: David E. Lilienthal's former place of residence, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Volpe, Joseph, Jr, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Waymack, William W, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Wigner, Eugene Paul, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Wilson, Carroll L, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Re World Bank - Meeting, New Delhi, India, 1958 October; 1 box (Box 410)
    - Re Yugoslavia, 1958; 1 box (Box 410)
  - Subseries 18D: 1959-1961, 19 boxes
    This subseries contains correspondence and related material from 1959 to 1961.
    - American Commercial Barge Line Company, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - American Committee on United Europe, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Abram, Morris B, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Re Argentina, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Arwin, Newton (Fred), 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Alumni Association, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Re Barge Lines, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Re Belgian Congo, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Biographical Sketch of David E. Lilienthal, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Black, Eugene R, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Bowles, Chester, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Re Brazil, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Brown, Edmund G, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Bucharia, Sister Maria, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Re California State Water Resources, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Casey, R.G., 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Chase, Stuart, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Clapp, Gordon R, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Cleveland Council on World Affairs, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Clifford, Clark, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Re Colombia CVC (Corporacion Autonoma Regional del Cauca), 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Cornell, Katharine, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1959; 1 box (Box 411)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Dietz, David, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Dillon, Douglas, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Dix, William S, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Douglas, William C, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Duffus, R.L., 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Re Durosol Project, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Eberstadt, Ferdinand, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Eccles, Marriner, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Ernst, Morris L, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Re Euratom, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Frankfurter, Felix, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Friendly, Fred M, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Fulbright, J. William, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Gandhi, Indira, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Garrison, Lloyd K, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Re Ghana, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Guistiniani, Piero, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Griffiths, Eldon W, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Gunther, John, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Harper & Brothers, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Harriman, W. Averell, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Harvard Law School, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Henderson, Loy, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Hewlett, Richard G, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Hixson, Jerome C, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Hoffman, Paul G, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Re India, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Re Indus River Basin, 1959; 1 box (Box 412)
    - Re Iran, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Israel-Trip, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Italconsult, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Re Italy, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Re Ivory Coast, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Re Jamaica, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Kazan, Elia, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Lazard Freres & Co, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Re Liberia, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Lilienthal, David E., Jr, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Lippmann, Walter, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Lleras, Alberto, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Makins, Roger, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Re Mexico, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Meyer, Andre, 1959; 1 box (Box 413)
    - Minerals & Chemicals Corporation, 1959; 1 box (Box 414)
    - Miscellaneous, 1959; 1 box (Box 414)
    - Monnet, Jean, 1959; 1 box (Box 414)
    - Monroney, Mike, 1959; 1 box (Box 414)
    - Re Morocco, 1959; 1 box (Box 414)
    - Murrow, Edward R, 1959; 1 box (Box 414)
    - Re Nigeria, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Nkrumah, Kwame, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Oxnam, Bishop G. Bromley, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Re Pakistan, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Patterson, Gardner, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Peccei, Aurelio, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Perkins, Milo, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Pflaum, Irving, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Re Philippines, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Re Publications by David E. Lilienthal, 1959 September 7; 1 box
      - Foreign Affairs, "Enterprise in Iran,", 1959 September 7; 1 box (Box 415)
      - TVA - Democracy On the March, Arabic Edition, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Radcliffe College, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Radio Corporation of America, (RCA), 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Reston, James, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Rockefeller, John D., III, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Rosenman, Samuel I, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur, Jr, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Re Somalia, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Twentieth Century Fund, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Re Venezuela, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Waymack, William W, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Wilson, Carroll L, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - Re Yugoslavia, 1959; 1 box (Box 415)
    - American Commercial Barge Line Company, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - American Committee on United Europe, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Re Argentina, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Arvin, Newton (Fred), 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Atomic Energy, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Ayub Khan, Mohammad, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Re Barge Lines, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Baruch, Bernard M, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Re Belgian Congo, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Berle, Adolf A., Jr, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Bingham, Jonathan B, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Black, Eugene R, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Bowles, Chester, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Brademas, John, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Re Brazil, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - Brookings Institution, 1960; 1 box (Box 416)
    - California State Water Resources, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Cherne, Leo, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Childs, Marquis, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Re China, People's Republic of, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Clapp, Gordon R, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Cleveland Council on World Affairs, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Cleveland, Harlan, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Clifford, Clark, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Re Colombia CVC (Corporacion Autonoma Regional del Cauca), 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Democratic National Committee, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Development and Resources Corporation, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Dillon, Douglas, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Douglas, William O, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Re Durisol Project, 1960; 1 box (Box 417)
    - Ebtehaj, A.H., 1960; 1 box (Box 418)
    - Elzia, Paul M, 1960; 1 box (Box 418)
    - Engle, Clair, 1960; 1 box (Box 418)
    - Field, George, 1960; 1 box (Box 418)
    - Finanziaria Italiana Di Investiment Azionari (FIDIA), 1960; 1 box (Box 418)
    - Finletter, Thomas K, 1960; 1 box (Box 418)